[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I don't know -- I don't think between want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "between", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", ",", "but", "I", "want", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "What did you think you'd be when you were young?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "you", "'d", "be", "when", "you", "were", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "A failure, a total starving (ph) failure.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "failure", ",", "a", "total", "starving", "(", "ph", ")", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "Did you ever imagine being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "being", "married", "to", "Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "In a different life, different world, it would have worked out very well.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "different", "life", ",", "different", "world", ",", "it", "would", "have", "worked", "out", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "And, Marlee, it's so stressful, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Marlee", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "stressful", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "(through interpreter): It's extremely stressful.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "It", "'s", "extremely", "stressful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "They're trying to break down you defenses, they're trying to get you emotionally and physically shattered, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "trying", "to", "break", "down", "you", "defenses", ",", "they", "'re", "trying", "to", "get", "you", "emotionally", "and", "physically", "shattered", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "(through interpreter): And yet it's up to you whether you want to take it that way.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "And", "yet", "it", "'s", "up", "to", "you", "whether", "you", "want", "to", "take", "it", "that", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1,150,000"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "And what were the charities?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "the", "charities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "(through interpreter): I raised $1,150,000.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "raised", "$", "1,150,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$800,000", "$130,000"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Saint Jude's Research Hospital"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "$", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "John?", "question_tokens": ["John", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I'm just under $800,000 for Saint Jude's Research Hospital, and then another $130,000 for other charities.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "under", "$", "800,000", "for", "Saint", "Jude", "'s", "Research", "Hospital", ",", "and", "then", "another", "$", "130,000", "for", "other", "charities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "There are other reasons, it certainly makes you feel good when you can raise that kind of money, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "other", "reasons", ",", "it", "certainly", "makes", "you", "feel", "good", "when", "you", "can", "raise", "that", "kind", "of", "money", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "(through interpreter): Well, exactly, I mean for me, the whole point for me was to do it for charity because I mean, clearly, it is exposure, people want to see what you can do beyond what they expect, what you might do in your career.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Well", ",", "exactly", ",", "I", "mean", "for", "me", ",", "the", "whole", "point", "for", "me", "was", "to", "do", "it", "for", "charity", "because", "I", "mean", ",", "clearly", ",", "it", "is", "exposure", ",", "people", "want", "to", "see", "what", "you", "can", "do", "beyond", "what", "they", "expect", ",", "what", "you", "might", "do", "in", "your", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Does it give you an advantage that the others heard you speaking in a male voice?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "give", "you", "an", "advantage", "that", "the", "others", "heard", "you", "speaking", "in", "a", "male", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "(through interpreter): Perhaps because they see me signing and they know that's it's me talking.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Perhaps", "because", "they", "see", "me", "signing", "and", "they", "know", "that", "'s", "it", "'s", "me", "talking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 130, "question": "And how embarrassed does he get when he has to talk about himself in the third person like this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "embarrassed", "does", "he", "get", "when", "he", "has", "to", "talk", "about", "himself", "in", "the", "third", "person", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "(through interpreter): Well, he loves it when he hears his own voice talking about him like that so --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Well", ",", "he", "loves", "it", "when", "he", "hears", "his", "own", "voice", "talking", "about", "him", "like", "that", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "I look at it as kind of like a privilege to experience being around such a relationship because how many people have ever even seen something like this in person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "look", "at", "it", "as", "kind", "of", "like", "a", "privilege", "to", "experience", "being", "around", "such", "a", "relationship", "because", "how", "many", "people", "have", "ever", "even", "seen", "something", "like", "this", "in", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "There's a quarter of a million dollars that could go to your charity, it's a really big deal, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "quarter", "of", "a", "million", "dollars", "that", "could", "go", "to", "your", "charity", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "really", "big", "deal", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "It's bigger than big.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "bigger", "than", "big", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Putting the charity to one side, are you surprised how competitive you became in this competition, in the sense of wanting to win?", "question_tokens": ["Putting", "the", "charity", "to", "one", "side", ",", "are", "you", "surprised", "how", "competitive", "you", "became", "in", "this", "competition", ",", "in", "the", "sense", "of", "wanting", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "What I'm surprised is that -- and you would never think a reality TV show would give you a life lesson, but it truly has to me.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "'m", "surprised", "is", "that", "--", "and", "you", "would", "never", "think", "a", "reality", "TV", "show", "would", "give", "you", "a", "life", "lesson", ",", "but", "it", "truly", "has", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["The Starkey Hearing Foundation"], "LOCATION": ["Minnesota"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Mostly incredibly hard work, mental challenges, competition with often erratic people what did you learn about yourselves and your character?", "question_tokens": ["Mostly", "incredibly", "hard", "work", ",", "mental", "challenges", ",", "competition", "with", "often", "erratic", "people", "what", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourselves", "and", "your", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "(through interpreter): I think -- well, coming into the show, I knew that I would be -- I mean, I would first try to raise as much money as I can for my charity, which again is The Starkey Hearing Foundation based in Minnesota.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "think", "--", "well", ",", "coming", "into", "the", "show", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "I", "would", "be", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "first", "try", "to", "raise", "as", "much", "money", "as", "I", "can", "for", "my", "charity", ",", "which", "again", "is", "The", "Starkey", "Hearing", "Foundation", "based", "in", "Minnesota", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "You have these four children, and yet you've been hit while you've been doing this show by a big financial crisis in your life, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "these", "four", "children", ",", "and", "yet", "you", "'ve", "been", "hit", "while", "you", "'ve", "been", "doing", "this", "show", "by", "a", "big", "financial", "crisis", "in", "your", "life", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "(through interpreter): You know, the financial crisis, it is what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "You", "know", ",", "the", "financial", "crisis", ",", "it", "is", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John", "John Rich"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "What am I going to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "I mean yes, if you're Little John out there John Rich is my mate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "yes", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "Little", "John", "out", "there", "John", "Rich", "is", "my", "mate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Well, I'm not real impressed with that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "real", "impressed", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Marlee, what do you hope this show will do for you?", "question_tokens": ["Marlee", ",", "what", "do", "you", "hope", "this", "show", "will", "do", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "(through interpreter): I would hope that it would give me the recognition of showing who I am in real life.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "would", "hope", "that", "it", "would", "give", "me", "the", "recognition", "of", "showing", "who", "I", "am", "in", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "John what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["John", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I think there's a stereotype that comes with cowboy hats.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "stereotype", "that", "comes", "with", "cowboy", "hats", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 348, "question": "And, Marlee, typical question for you, but I'm going to ask you anyway, if you could live without one of two men, your husband or Jack -- who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Marlee", ",", "typical", "question", "for", "you", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "ask", "you", "anyway", ",", "if", "you", "could", "live", "without", "one", "of", "two", "men", ",", "your", "husband", "or", "Jack", "--", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "(through interpreter): I've had my husband for 18 years, I've had four kids with him, and I'm an extremely happily married woman --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "'ve", "had", "my", "husband", "for", "18", "years", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "four", "kids", "with", "him", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "an", "extremely", "happily", "married", "woman", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"], "LOCATION": ["Marlee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "You should just leave the set.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "just", "leave", "the", "set", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 374, "question": "How do your children deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "your", "children", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "(through interpreter): You mean deal with what, my celebrity or my deafness, or me going away --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "You", "mean", "deal", "with", "what", ",", "my", "celebrity", "or", "my", "deafness", ",", "or", "me", "going", "away", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "How do you converse with them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "converse", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "(through interpreter): They don't know any other way.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "They", "do", "n't", "know", "any", "other", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Can they all do the sign language?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "they", "all", "do", "the", "sign", "language", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "(through interpreter): They sign if they feel like it.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "They", "sign", "if", "they", "feel", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [",", "``", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "DT", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "If they don't want to listen to their mother, they don't bother, right?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "listen", "to", "their", "mother", ",", "they", "do", "n't", "bother", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": ", (through interpreter): No, listen, I can't -- that's actually a good point.", "answer_tokens": [",", "(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "No", ",", "listen", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "that", "'s", "actually", "a", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "What do you think President Trump would've been like for this country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "President", "Trump", "would", "'ve", "been", "like", "for", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I would've like to have seen him in a debate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "'ve", "like", "to", "have", "seen", "him", "in", "a", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What do you think Marlee?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "Marlee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "(through translator): You know, I'm stunned, but I'm more eager to roll up my sleeves and just jump in it and see what you got for us.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "translator", ")", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "stunned", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "more", "eager", "to", "roll", "up", "my", "sleeves", "and", "just", "jump", "in", "it", "and", "see", "what", "you", "got", "for", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "But let's just -- let's cut the crap shall we, you both want to kill each other in the final right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "let", "'s", "just", "--", "let", "'s", "cut", "the", "crap", "shall", "we", ",", "you", "both", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "(through interpreter): Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I don't about -- I don't think we want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "about", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", ",", "but", "I", "want", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "You are, because every Christmas in Britain, I sort of familiar regime.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", ",", "because", "every", "Christmas", "in", "Britain", ",", "I", "sort", "of", "familiar", "regime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Can you still do that God awful Cockney accent that you did?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "do", "that", "God", "awful", "Cockney", "accent", "that", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I can do the bad one that I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "do", "the", "bad", "one", "that", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "I don't think I can -- what would be a line?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "can", "--", "what", "would", "be", "a", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Don't pretend to be me.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "pretend", "to", "be", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Have you been to the Cockney part of London?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "to", "the", "Cockney", "part", "of", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Do they laugh at you or with you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "laugh", "at", "you", "or", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What do you think your great talent is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "your", "great", "talent", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What did you think you would be when you were younger?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "you", "would", "be", "when", "you", "were", "younger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "A failure, a total starving failure.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "failure", ",", "a", "total", "starving", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "CD", ":", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You have been clean for how long now?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "been", "clean", "for", "how", "long", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Oh, 25 -- more than 25 years now.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "25", "--", "more", "than", "25", "years", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "How bad was it at its worst for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "was", "it", "at", "its", "worst", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Having a hangover so bad that I could hardly -- shaking, splitting headaches, and having to go to work.", "answer_tokens": ["Having", "a", "hangover", "so", "bad", "that", "I", "could", "hardly", "--", "shaking", ",", "splitting", "headaches", ",", "and", "having", "to", "go", "to", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "VBD", ":", "CD", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "How much would you be drinking?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "would", "you", "be", "drinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I probably -- that was -- eight, ten drinks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "probably", "--", "that", "was", "--", "eight", ",", "ten", "drinks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Were you?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Did that make you feel slightly uneasy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "slightly", "uneasy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Very uneasy, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "uneasy", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "You never had a drink again?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "had", "a", "drink", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "AN DYKE: No.", "answer_tokens": ["AN", "DYKE", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Do you wish you could have a glass of wine over a meal or something?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "you", "could", "have", "a", "glass", "of", "wine", "over", "a", "meal", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Don't miss it all.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "miss", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Why did you give up cigarettes?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "give", "up", "cigarettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I had a doctor tell me I had an emphysema scar, a man I didn't even know, a little East Indian doctor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "doctor", "tell", "me", "I", "had", "an", "emphysema", "scar", ",", "a", "man", "I", "did", "n't", "even", "know", ",", "a", "little", "East", "Indian", "doctor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 629, "question": "How about the baby?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "the", "baby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Only your mother would think --", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "your", "mother", "would", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "How important -- obviously it's important, but how important is chemistry between a leading man and lady?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "--", "obviously", "it", "'s", "important", ",", "but", "how", "important", "is", "chemistry", "between", "a", "leading", "man", "and", "lady", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "In my case, extremely important.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "case", ",", "extremely", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Mary Tyler Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Could you have ever imagined being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "have", "ever", "imagined", "being", "married", "to", "Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "In a different life, in a different world, it probably would have worked out very well, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "different", "life", ",", "in", "a", "different", "world", ",", "it", "probably", "would", "have", "worked", "out", "very", "well", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "How can Dick Van Dyke be 85?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "Dick", "Van", "Dyke", "be", "85", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "It's a surprise to me because I'm still -- I just did a show where I danced and sang.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "surprise", "to", "me", "because", "I", "'m", "still", "--", "I", "just", "did", "a", "show", "where", "I", "danced", "and", "sang", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Van Dyke"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Which of all of them impressed you the most?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "all", "of", "them", "impressed", "you", "the", "most", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "ORGAN: Why?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "He was so cordial.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "so", "cordial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "That's quite something, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "quite", "something", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Why don't you say I'm going to go lie by the pool?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "say", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "lie", "by", "the", "pool", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Well, I've retired hundreds of times and it never worked out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "retired", "hundreds", "of", "times", "and", "it", "never", "worked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Because I enjoy -- I enjoy it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "enjoy", "--", "I", "enjoy", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "proud", "of", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "What do you think the secret of true love is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "secret", "of", "true", "love", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "AN DYKE: You have to care about the welfare of the other person.", "answer_tokens": ["AN", "DYKE", ":", "You", "have", "to", "care", "about", "the", "welfare", "of", "the", "other", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "How many times have you had that feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "had", "that", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Three.", "answer_tokens": ["Three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Do you think you may ever get remarried?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "may", "ever", "get", "remarried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "You're never going to give up, are you, Dick?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "never", "going", "to", "give", "up", ",", "are", "you", ",", "Dick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "What did he say you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "I", "'m", "Barack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "He didn't say that?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "He did.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "moment", "--", "when", "Michelle", "was", "dating", "Barack", ",", "when", "was", "the", "moment", "that", "you", "realized", "this", "guy", "may", "be", "something", "special", "politically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "no", "idea", "at", "the", "time", "when", "I", "met", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Barack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "ORGAN: You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "I don't know -- I don't think between want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "between", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", ",", "but", "I", "want", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "What did you think you'd be when you were young?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "you", "'d", "be", "when", "you", "were", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "A failure, a total starving (ph) failure.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "failure", ",", "a", "total", "starving", "(", "ph", ")", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Did you ever imagine being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "being", "married", "to", "Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "In a different life, different world, it would have worked out very well.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "different", "life", ",", "different", "world", ",", "it", "would", "have", "worked", "out", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "And, Marlee, it's so stressful, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Marlee", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "stressful", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "(through interpreter): It's extremely stressful.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "It", "'s", "extremely", "stressful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "They're trying to break down you defenses, they're trying to get you emotionally and physically shattered, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "trying", "to", "break", "down", "you", "defenses", ",", "they", "'re", "trying", "to", "get", "you", "emotionally", "and", "physically", "shattered", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "(through interpreter): And yet it's up to you whether you want to take it that way.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "And", "yet", "it", "'s", "up", "to", "you", "whether", "you", "want", "to", "take", "it", "that", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1,150,000"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "And what were the charities?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "the", "charities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "(through interpreter): I raised $1,150,000.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "raised", "$", "1,150,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$800,000", "$130,000"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Saint Jude's Research Hospital"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "$", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "$", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "John?", "question_tokens": ["John", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "I'm just under $800,000 for Saint Jude's Research Hospital, and then another $130,000 for other charities.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "under", "$", "800,000", "for", "Saint", "Jude", "'s", "Research", "Hospital", ",", "and", "then", "another", "$", "130,000", "for", "other", "charities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "There are other reasons, it certainly makes you feel good when you can raise that kind of money, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "other", "reasons", ",", "it", "certainly", "makes", "you", "feel", "good", "when", "you", "can", "raise", "that", "kind", "of", "money", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "(through interpreter): Well, exactly, I mean for me, the whole point for me was to do it for charity because I mean, clearly, it is exposure, people want to see what you can do beyond what they expect, what you might do in your career.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Well", ",", "exactly", ",", "I", "mean", "for", "me", ",", "the", "whole", "point", "for", "me", "was", "to", "do", "it", "for", "charity", "because", "I", "mean", ",", "clearly", ",", "it", "is", "exposure", ",", "people", "want", "to", "see", "what", "you", "can", "do", "beyond", "what", "they", "expect", ",", "what", "you", "might", "do", "in", "your", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "Does it give you an advantage that the others heard you speaking in a male voice?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "give", "you", "an", "advantage", "that", "the", "others", "heard", "you", "speaking", "in", "a", "male", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "(through interpreter): Perhaps because they see me signing and they know that's it's me talking.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Perhaps", "because", "they", "see", "me", "signing", "and", "they", "know", "that", "'s", "it", "'s", "me", "talking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 907, "question": "And how embarrassed does he get when he has to talk about himself in the third person like this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "embarrassed", "does", "he", "get", "when", "he", "has", "to", "talk", "about", "himself", "in", "the", "third", "person", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 908, "answer": "(through interpreter): Well, he loves it when he hears his own voice talking about him like that so --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Well", ",", "he", "loves", "it", "when", "he", "hears", "his", "own", "voice", "talking", "about", "him", "like", "that", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 918, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 919, "answer": "I look at it as kind of like a privilege to experience being around such a relationship because how many people have ever even seen something like this in person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "look", "at", "it", "as", "kind", "of", "like", "a", "privilege", "to", "experience", "being", "around", "such", "a", "relationship", "because", "how", "many", "people", "have", "ever", "even", "seen", "something", "like", "this", "in", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 946, "question": "There's a quarter of a million dollars that could go to your charity, it's a really big deal, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "quarter", "of", "a", "million", "dollars", "that", "could", "go", "to", "your", "charity", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "really", "big", "deal", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 947, "answer": "It's bigger than big.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "bigger", "than", "big", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["million dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 956, "question": "Putting the charity to one side, are you surprised how competitive you became in this competition, in the sense of wanting to win?", "question_tokens": ["Putting", "the", "charity", "to", "one", "side", ",", "are", "you", "surprised", "how", "competitive", "you", "became", "in", "this", "competition", ",", "in", "the", "sense", "of", "wanting", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 957, "answer": "What I'm surprised is that -- and you would never think a reality TV show would give you a life lesson, but it truly has to me.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "'m", "surprised", "is", "that", "--", "and", "you", "would", "never", "think", "a", "reality", "TV", "show", "would", "give", "you", "a", "life", "lesson", ",", "but", "it", "truly", "has", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["The Starkey Hearing Foundation"], "LOCATION": ["Minnesota"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 971, "question": "Mostly incredibly hard work, mental challenges, competition with often erratic people what did you learn about yourselves and your character?", "question_tokens": ["Mostly", "incredibly", "hard", "work", ",", "mental", "challenges", ",", "competition", "with", "often", "erratic", "people", "what", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourselves", "and", "your", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 972, "answer": "(through interpreter): I think -- well, coming into the show, I knew that I would be -- I mean, I would first try to raise as much money as I can for my charity, which again is The Starkey Hearing Foundation based in Minnesota.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "think", "--", "well", ",", "coming", "into", "the", "show", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "I", "would", "be", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "first", "try", "to", "raise", "as", "much", "money", "as", "I", "can", "for", "my", "charity", ",", "which", "again", "is", "The", "Starkey", "Hearing", "Foundation", "based", "in", "Minnesota", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1047, "question": "You have these four children, and yet you've been hit while you've been doing this show by a big financial crisis in your life, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "these", "four", "children", ",", "and", "yet", "you", "'ve", "been", "hit", "while", "you", "'ve", "been", "doing", "this", "show", "by", "a", "big", "financial", "crisis", "in", "your", "life", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1048, "answer": "(through interpreter): You know, the financial crisis, it is what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "You", "know", ",", "the", "financial", "crisis", ",", "it", "is", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John", "John Rich"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1080, "question": "What am I going to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1081, "answer": "I mean yes, if you're Little John out there John Rich is my mate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "yes", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "Little", "John", "out", "there", "John", "Rich", "is", "my", "mate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 1106, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1107, "answer": "Well, I'm not real impressed with that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "real", "impressed", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1112, "question": "Marlee, what do you hope this show will do for you?", "question_tokens": ["Marlee", ",", "what", "do", "you", "hope", "this", "show", "will", "do", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1113, "answer": "(through interpreter): I would hope that it would give me the recognition of showing who I am in real life.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "would", "hope", "that", "it", "would", "give", "me", "the", "recognition", "of", "showing", "who", "I", "am", "in", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1117, "question": "John what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["John", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1118, "answer": "I think there's a stereotype that comes with cowboy hats.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "stereotype", "that", "comes", "with", "cowboy", "hats", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1125, "question": "And, Marlee, typical question for you, but I'm going to ask you anyway, if you could live without one of two men, your husband or Jack -- who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Marlee", ",", "typical", "question", "for", "you", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "ask", "you", "anyway", ",", "if", "you", "could", "live", "without", "one", "of", "two", "men", ",", "your", "husband", "or", "Jack", "--", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1126, "answer": "(through interpreter): I've had my husband for 18 years, I've had four kids with him, and I'm an extremely happily married woman --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "I", "'ve", "had", "my", "husband", "for", "18", "years", ",", "I", "'ve", "had", "four", "kids", "with", "him", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "an", "extremely", "happily", "married", "woman", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"], "LOCATION": ["Marlee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1135, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 1136, "answer": "You should just leave the set.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "just", "leave", "the", "set", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 1151, "question": "How do your children deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "your", "children", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1152, "answer": "(through interpreter): You mean deal with what, my celebrity or my deafness, or me going away --", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "You", "mean", "deal", "with", "what", ",", "my", "celebrity", "or", "my", "deafness", ",", "or", "me", "going", "away", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1154, "question": "How do you converse with them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "converse", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1155, "answer": "(through interpreter): They don't know any other way.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "They", "do", "n't", "know", "any", "other", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1158, "question": "Can they all do the sign language?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "they", "all", "do", "the", "sign", "language", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1159, "answer": "(through interpreter): They sign if they feel like it.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "They", "sign", "if", "they", "feel", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [",", "``", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "DT", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1161, "question": "If they don't want to listen to their mother, they don't bother, right?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "listen", "to", "their", "mother", ",", "they", "do", "n't", "bother", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1162, "answer": ", (through interpreter): No, listen, I can't -- that's actually a good point.", "answer_tokens": [",", "(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "No", ",", "listen", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "that", "'s", "actually", "a", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1174, "question": "What do you think President Trump would've been like for this country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "President", "Trump", "would", "'ve", "been", "like", "for", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1175, "answer": "I would've like to have seen him in a debate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "'ve", "like", "to", "have", "seen", "him", "in", "a", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1224, "question": "What do you think Marlee?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "Marlee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1225, "answer": "(through translator): You know, I'm stunned, but I'm more eager to roll up my sleeves and just jump in it and see what you got for us.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "translator", ")", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "stunned", ",", "but", "I", "'m", "more", "eager", "to", "roll", "up", "my", "sleeves", "and", "just", "jump", "in", "it", "and", "see", "what", "you", "got", "for", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1244, "question": "But let's just -- let's cut the crap shall we, you both want to kill each other in the final right?", "question_tokens": ["But", "let", "'s", "just", "--", "let", "'s", "cut", "the", "crap", "shall", "we", ",", "you", "both", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1245, "answer": "(through interpreter): Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "through", "interpreter", ")", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1248, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", "in", "the", "final", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1249, "answer": "I don't about -- I don't think we want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "about", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "want", "to", "kill", "each", "other", ",", "but", "I", "want", "to", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1275, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 1276, "answer": "You are, because every Christmas in Britain, I sort of familiar regime.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", ",", "because", "every", "Christmas", "in", "Britain", ",", "I", "sort", "of", "familiar", "regime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1281, "question": "Can you still do that God awful Cockney accent that you did?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "do", "that", "God", "awful", "Cockney", "accent", "that", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 1282, "answer": "I can do the bad one that I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "do", "the", "bad", "one", "that", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1286, "question": "I don't think I can -- what would be a line?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "can", "--", "what", "would", "be", "a", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1287, "answer": "Don't pretend to be me.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "pretend", "to", "be", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1296, "question": "Have you been to the Cockney part of London?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "to", "the", "Cockney", "part", "of", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1297, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1299, "question": "Do they laugh at you or with you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "laugh", "at", "you", "or", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1300, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1306, "question": "What do you think your great talent is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "your", "great", "talent", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1307, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1318, "question": "What did you think you would be when you were younger?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "you", "would", "be", "when", "you", "were", "younger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 1319, "answer": "A failure, a total starving failure.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "failure", ",", "a", "total", "starving", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "CD", ":", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1332, "question": "You have been clean for how long now?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "been", "clean", "for", "how", "long", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1333, "answer": "Oh, 25 -- more than 25 years now.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "25", "--", "more", "than", "25", "years", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1354, "question": "How bad was it at its worst for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "bad", "was", "it", "at", "its", "worst", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1355, "answer": "Having a hangover so bad that I could hardly -- shaking, splitting headaches, and having to go to work.", "answer_tokens": ["Having", "a", "hangover", "so", "bad", "that", "I", "could", "hardly", "--", "shaking", ",", "splitting", "headaches", ",", "and", "having", "to", "go", "to", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "VBD", ":", "CD", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1356, "question": "How much would you be drinking?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "would", "you", "be", "drinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1357, "answer": "I probably -- that was -- eight, ten drinks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "probably", "--", "that", "was", "--", "eight", ",", "ten", "drinks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1364, "question": "Were you?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1365, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1368, "question": "Did that make you feel slightly uneasy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "slightly", "uneasy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1369, "answer": "Very uneasy, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "uneasy", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1371, "question": "You never had a drink again?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "had", "a", "drink", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1372, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 1379, "question": "Do you wish you could have a glass of wine over a meal or something?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "wish", "you", "could", "have", "a", "glass", "of", "wine", "over", "a", "meal", "or", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1380, "answer": "Don't miss it all.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "miss", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1384, "question": "Why did you give up cigarettes?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "give", "up", "cigarettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1385, "answer": "I had a doctor tell me I had an emphysema scar, a man I didn't even know, a little East Indian doctor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "doctor", "tell", "me", "I", "had", "an", "emphysema", "scar", ",", "a", "man", "I", "did", "n't", "even", "know", ",", "a", "little", "East", "Indian", "doctor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 1406, "question": "How about the baby?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "the", "baby", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1407, "answer": "Only your mother would think --", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "your", "mother", "would", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1424, "question": "How important -- obviously it's important, but how important is chemistry between a leading man and lady?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "--", "obviously", "it", "'s", "important", ",", "but", "how", "important", "is", "chemistry", "between", "a", "leading", "man", "and", "lady", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1425, "answer": "In my case, extremely important.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "my", "case", ",", "extremely", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1434, "question": "Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1435, "answer": "Mary Tyler Moore.", "answer_tokens": ["Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1441, "question": "Could you have ever imagined being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "have", "ever", "imagined", "being", "married", "to", "Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1442, "answer": "In a different life, in a different world, it probably would have worked out very well, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "different", "life", ",", "in", "a", "different", "world", ",", "it", "probably", "would", "have", "worked", "out", "very", "well", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary Tyler Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1449, "question": "How can Dick Van Dyke be 85?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "Dick", "Van", "Dyke", "be", "85", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 1450, "answer": "It's a surprise to me because I'm still -- I just did a show where I danced and sang.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "surprise", "to", "me", "because", "I", "'m", "still", "--", "I", "just", "did", "a", "show", "where", "I", "danced", "and", "sang", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick Van Dyke"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1456, "question": "Which of all of them impressed you the most?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "of", "all", "of", "them", "impressed", "you", "the", "most", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "."], "aSentId": 1457, "answer": "Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1459, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1460, "answer": "He was so cordial.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "so", "cordial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1471, "question": "That's quite something, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "quite", "something", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1472, "answer": "Oh yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 1475, "question": "Why don't you say I'm going to go lie by the pool?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "say", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "lie", "by", "the", "pool", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1476, "answer": "Well, I've retired hundreds of times and it never worked out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "retired", "hundreds", "of", "times", "and", "it", "never", "worked", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1477, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 1478, "answer": "Because I enjoy -- I enjoy it.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "enjoy", "--", "I", "enjoy", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1491, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "proud", "of", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1492, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1500, "question": "What do you think the secret of true love is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "secret", "of", "true", "love", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1501, "answer": "You have to care about the welfare of the other person.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "care", "about", "the", "welfare", "of", "the", "other", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 1502, "question": "How many times have you had that feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "had", "that", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 1503, "answer": "Three.", "answer_tokens": ["Three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1509, "question": "Do you think you may ever get remarried?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "may", "ever", "get", "remarried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 1510, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1514, "question": "You're never going to give up, are you, Dick?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "never", "going", "to", "give", "up", ",", "are", "you", ",", "Dick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1515, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1526, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1527, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack"]}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1529, "question": "What did he say you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1530, "answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "I", "'m", "Barack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 1531, "question": "He didn't say that?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1532, "answer": "He did.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110520pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1541, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "moment", "--", "when", "Michelle", "was", "dating", "Barack", ",", "when", "was", "the", "moment", "that", "you", "realized", "this", "guy", "may", "be", "something", "special", "politically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1542, "answer": "I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "no", "idea", "at", "the", "time", "when", "I", "met", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Barack"]}}]